

INTRODUCTION

A self-motivated, committed individual enthusiastic about pursuing a career in the technological sector in Singapore.

I have experience with Python, HTML, CSS and Javascript – Mostly self-taught. My projects can be found in the website links below.

CONTACT

PHONE: 90099178

WEBSITE:

jspoh.github.io github.com/jspoh

EMAIL:

jingsengpoh@gmail.com

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/js-poh

HOBBIES

Kickboxing Piano Gaming

POH JING SENG

EDUCATION

Singapore University of Social Sciences

BSc in Information and Communications Technology Jul 2022 – Present

Incheon National University

Aug 2018 – Jan 2019 Semester exchange program

Nanyang Polytechnic

Apr 2017 – Apr 2020 Diploma in Business Management Specialisation in Human Resource Management, International Business

WORK EXPERIENCE (OVERVIEW)

Singapore Armed Forces

May 2020 – Aug 2022 Guard Commander

Air Force Recruitment Centre

Sep 2020 – Dec 2020 Officer recruitment processing assistant

WBL Engineering & Distribution

Nov 2019 – Feb 2020 Human Resources Intern

Careerlink @ NYP

Sep 2019 – Nov 2019 Human Resources Intern

CERTIFICATIONS

- Python(Basic) Certificate HackerRank
- WSQ Certificate in Security SAF MP Command
- FB-RM-102C-1 Follow food and beverage safety and hygiene policies and procedures

WORK EXPERIENCE (DETAILED)

Singapore Armed Forces

May 2020 - Aug 2022

Guard Commander

- Responsibilities
 - o Planned and drafted duty rosters every 2-3 days
 - In charge of daily operations, including responding to alarms and emergencies
 - Conducted trainings and assessments
 - o Liaised effectively with multiple contractors on a monthly basis to respond to infrastructure faults
 - o Management of conflicts between my subordinates and others
 - o Information gathering and writing incident reports
 - o Took care of the welfare and health of my subordinates
 - Ensured timeliness of certain operational demands for Search And Rescue(SAR) missions in which many lives have been saved
 - o Maintained a high standard of discipline and performance in my subordinates
- Awards
 - o Best in knowledge Force protection term at Tengah Airbase
 - o Best airman of the month July 2021
 - o High Achiever Award March 2022
 - o Best airman of the month April 2022
 - o 605SQN Command Chief coin recipient
 - o 606SQN Commanding Officer coin recipient
- Accepted an offer to extend my service

Air Force Recruitment Centre

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

Officer recruitment processing assistant / Pilot(trainee)

- Responsibilities
 - o Liaised with prospective applicants on application information
 - Medical appointments
 - Web briefings
 - Document submissions
 - Contract signings
 - o Clarified applicants' concerns
 - o Ensured smooth daily operations for my superior

WBL Engineering & Distribution

Nov 2019 – Feb 2020 Human Resources Intern

- Responsibilities
 - Handled the entire spectrum of recruitment functions
 - Talent acquisition
 - Resume and phone screenings
 - Conducting of interviews
 - Drafting salary proposals
 - Preparation and facilitation of contract signings
 - Coordination of employee orientations
 - Filing of employee documents and entering details into Human Resources Information System(HRIS)
 - Refreshing of Job Description depositories and writing up new ones in accordance to ISO requirements
 - Set-up training plans for employees for the work year 2020
 - Researched and presented ITE, Polytechnics and Universities internship data
 - Supported HRIS migration from Prosoft to BIPO
 - Planning and execution of employee engagement events (Chinese new year and helping out at an elderly home)
 - Attendance of over 70 employees

Careerlink @ NYP

Sep 2019 - Nov 2020

Human Resources Intern

- Conducted talent acquisition processes for multiple companies
 - o Designing of job posters for advertising
 - o Cold calling and emailing potential talents
 - o Conducted interviews and selections
 - o Recommending prospective candidates to company HR managers
- Spearheaded the planning and execution of employee engagement event(Games day)
 - o 100% employee satisfaction rate
- Handled projects for multiple companies
 - o Natsteel
 - Planned and executed the "Bring your family to work day 2019" employee engagement event with over 100 employees turning up
 - o Heinemann
 - Creation of employee value propositions
 - o Dentons Rodyk
 - Deriving low cost and practical solutions from the training needs analysis for secretaries